http://www.earthsongfibers.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Home
Log In
Categories
Books & VideosChilden's BooksCrochet & HookingDyeingFeltingGeneral & VariousKnittingSpinning & CardingVideos - DVD/VHSWeavingCardingAshford CardersLouet CardersSchacht CardersDyeingNatural DyesEarthues DyesDyeing SuppliesSynthetic DyesCountry ClassicGaywool DyesJacquard DyesFeltingKnit and FeltAnimal KitsPatternsNeedle FeltingPlant DyedYarnBooksWet FeltingFelting FiberKitsToolsSoles & PalmsFelting Books & VideosKits & CraftsChildren's BooksFriendly LoomsKits & ProjectsPlant Dyed YarnKnitting & CrochetCrochet HooksKnitting NeedlesSlipper Soles / Mitten PalmsKnitting AccessoriesMoth ControlPatternsFiber Trends PatternsAccessoriesAnimals, Toys & Various DelightsBabies & ChildrenShawls & LaceSoles & PalmsSweaters & VestsCottage CreationsSpinning FibersAshland Bay FibersEarthsong Orchard FarmFoxglove FibersLouet FibersSpinning Wheels & SuppliesAshford SpinningAshford Spinning SuppliesAshford Spinning WheelsKromski SpinningKromski Spinning SuppliesSchacht SpinningSchacht Spinning SuppliesSchacht Spinning WheelsSpinning ExtrasWeaving Looms & SuppliesAshford Looms & Weaving SuppliesAshford LoomsAshford Weaving SuppliesHarrisville Looms & WeavingKromski Weaving SuppliesSchacht Looms & Weaving SuppliesSchacht Table LoomsSchacht Wolf LoomsSchacht Weaving SuppliesWool WashingYarnAshford YarnsBrown Sheep YarnGreen MountainHeavenly HuesSteadfast FibersGift CertificatesSpecials ...All Products ...
Information
About Us
Shipping
Privacy Notice
Contact Us
Returns
Site Map
Gift Certificate FAQ
More Information
WebRings
Earthsong Orchard Farm
Specials  [more]
Circular Addi Natura Bamboo Needles 32"$13.95  $10.46Save: 25% off
Search
Advanced Search
Cards Accepted
Home >
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Earthsong Fibers Privacy Policy ...
At Earthsong Fibers, your privacy is our priority. We are committed to protecting your privacy at all times, in all situations. The information we collect about you when you become a member is used to process your orders and to provide a more personalized experience on our site. Our site uses a 128 bit encrypted SSL to increase the security of our customer’s information.
How Do We Use the Information We Collect?
When you become an Earthsong Fibers member, we ask you to fill out a form that requests your name, address and e-mail address as well as some demographic information such as gender and date of birth.
Your name and address information is used solely to process orders and will NEVER be sold, given, rented or traded to others for purposes other than order fulfillment. Your demographic information (gender, date of birth, etc.) will be used for several security purposes, to ensure you are who you say you are and in fact you are paying with your credit cards and not someone using your stolen credit cards.
Refer-A-Friend
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. www.earthsongfibers.com does not store this information and uses it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.
Our Use of Log Files
When you visit our site we automatically log your IP address, your browser type and your access times. We utilize this information to conduct site performance evaluations, to see where visitors are coming from and to keep track of click stream data (the screens our users visit on our site). This data helps us to determine what content our members find most appealing so that we can maximize your enjoyment of the site. Log files are not tied to personally identifiable information.
Site Security
All www.earthsongfibers.com employees take your personal information very seriously.
The information is ID and password protected and our Web security is reviewed on a monthly basis. We have also installed and implied our site with a 128 bit encryption SSL.
Correcting/Updating
Your Personal Information After becoming an www.earthsongfibers.com subscriber you may correct/update your personal information by clicking on the 'My Account' link at the top of any page, entering your ID, password and birth date when prompted and clicking the Edit Information button. The changes you make will be reflected in our databases instantly. If you wish to deactivate your account, you may contact us through the 'My Account' section, or the 'Contact Us' section.
Links To Other Sites
This Web site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you may be leaving the www.earthsongfibers.com site and entering another Web site. These sites may independently collect or request information about you and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.
Communication
From time to time we may send out email messages alerting you that products are available, to remind you about providing feedback or for promotional offers. In addition, you will receive communication from us 1) if you contact us for a particular reason, 2) to receive your orders, or 3) we need to contact you for administrative purposes such as winning a contest. Administrative e-mails will not contain promotional materials. If you choose to receive our News Letters, they will contain promotional materials from www.earthsongfibers.com.
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site
Supplementation
We may correct or supplement your address information with standardized postal representation in order to ensure that your orders are delivered. We do this since we want to make sure that our members receive the order and to lower costs associated with our programs.
Our Use of Cookies
Cookies are pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer's hard drive which identify you when you enter. The ability to select samples on our site is not cookie-driven. We may use session cookies to provide a seamless experience on the site and to combine with our log files so that we can understand our site traffic and analyze our demographic information in aggregate form. If you have set your browser to reject cookies, our site will not identify you when you enter and you will need to manually type in your ID and password.
Your Feedback is Always Welcome
We welcome your comments and questions about our privacy policy - or anything else you might want to talk about. To contact us click here.
Your IP Address is:
72.182.10.230
Copyright © 2020 Earthsong Fibers. Powered by Zen Cart
Parse Time: 0.157 - Number of Queries: 51 - Query Time: 0.055596946975708
